Blessed by heaven and earth,
the Chaos Pearl was born.
The Supreme Lord
split it into two.
The celestial energy within
became the Spirit Pearl,
while the demonic energy
formed the Demon Orb.
A Wrath of Heaven curse
was cast on the Demon Orb,
set to destroy it with
lightning in three years.
Later, due to Shen
Gongbao's intervening,
the Demon Orb reincarnated as Nezha,
third son of Li Jing in Chentang Pass.
The Spirit Pearl became Ao Bing, also
the third son of the Dragon King.
By fate,
the two became best friends.
Nezha, influenced
by his parents,
shed his demonic nature,
and saved Chentang Pass.
Together with Ao Bing,
they faced the Wrath of Heaven,
and at last
changed their destinies.
Ne Zha 2
Though you've
survived the wrath,
but your bodies
were destroyed...
without which
the soul will soon
fade into oblivion.
The Sacred Lotus protects
and nurtures spirit.
I will now use it to recreate
your physical forms.
Wow Stunning
Start up!
Something's off...
Is there?
The lotus root must be powdered
to make your bodies.
Did you just scratch
your feet with that hand?
Oh, don't worry.
I don't mind sticky foot,
a quick wash will fix it.
It's not your foot I care.
Did you just blow your
nose with that hand?
No, nothing.
It's just lotus powder.
See? Lotus powder.
It's ready to go.
Here, come on.
One booger for each of you.
I mean one serving.
Chop chop! To save your souls.
I'd rather...
Pain the ass, little bastard!
It works!
Hang on.
What is this?
Thanks to you.
I've been looking all over.
Time for shaping.
Flying Pig's memory
is unmatched,
so is his carving skills.
Perfect renovation, right?
Thanks, Piggy.
Don't move, your
body's not fixed yet.
Master Immortal,
I've mobilized all
of Chentang's forces
on guarding of Shen Gongbao
and the Eastern Sea dragons.
Take it easy.
The dragons are watching
the Abyss monsters,
none of which would escape.
Shen Gongbao alone is no threat.
You should check this out.
Isn't this impeccable?
Woah!
He learned from the best.
But,
does it have to be
exactly the same?
Can't you make me look better?
Huh?
That's right.
Parents always want the
best for the kids, huh?
Right.
Make me tall and hunky.
Also hauntingly handsome
A man must be strong and lofty.
As well as demure and mindful.
But also cute and lovable.
Can you all make up your mind?
Tall and hunky,
With a touch of handsomeness.
Strong and lofty.
Yet super adorable.
What's this?
He said... Start your
performance then.
Come on!
I should've taken over earlier.
DIY is always the best.
This could take awhile.
Let's do you first.
You were born of
the water element,
so you must be
tempered by pure water.
Open Lotus!
Here we go.
Are you done?
Almost...
This version is surely
the most dazzling,
but fine-tuning will
take a long time.
How about we just use
the first one for now?
Yeah, the first version will do.
I agree.
Right.
You were born of
the fire element,
so you must be refined
in pure flames.
Sir!
Enemy has been spotted at sea.
It seems to be Sheg Gongbao.
How many?
Just him.
How come?
Carry on with your spell.
We'll handle the intruder.
Master Immortal,
let me go plead with my master.
Don't move!
Before another incense
stick is fully burnt,
your body won't be fixed.
Shen Gongbao,
to what do we owe this honor?
Now that you know of my
plan with the dragons,
I can't help but
feel un... uneasy.
Chentang Pass is
heavily guarded,
and Master Taiyi
is within the city.
You, alone, won't
accomplish much.
Who... who said I'm alone?
[Two hours ago, Dragon Palace]
If they find out about
the Spirit Pearl,
not only will you fail
to avenge your son,
[Queen of Western Sea] not only
will you fail to avenge your son,
but the entire Eastern Dragon
Clan [Queen of Western Sea]
[Dragon King of Eastern Sea] but
the entire Eastern Dragon Clan
will bear the blame.
[Dragon King of Eastern Sea]
When the truth comes out,
you'll be cast into
the abyss purgatory,
[Dragon King of Southern Sea] you'll
be cast into the abyss purgatory,
surrounded by all your old "fellows".
[Dragon King of Southern Sea]
Let's see how we welcome you.
Being stuck in Dragon Palace...
[Dragon King of Northern Sea]
How could you avenge your son?
Even I feel nervous for you.
You fools are in
no place to gloat.
Was simply trying to help.
But it seems that you
don't appreciate it.
Hmm?
You must've forgotten
what I'm capable of.
Ah!
I know this one.
The Sky... Sky... Sky...
Sky Splitting Claw.
Thank you.
Master Shen can take this
claw to Chentang Pass,
and use it to tear open a
rift leading back to me.
The Abyss Monsters can then
help you destroy your enemy.
[Sky-Splitting Thunder Whip]
The Abyss Monsters?
How... is that possible?
They were trapped by the
Suppression Seal for thousand years.
How could they possibly escape?
The dragons... have they
already released them?
With the Sea-Stabilizing
Chains binding us,
there's no chance for escape.
This is a win-win tactic.
What do you say, my brother?
You wouldn't be so generous.
Get to the point.
What's your price?
In this purgatory,
where flames burn our bodies,
every day feels like a year.
If you could slightly
lower the lava's heat,
easing our suffering,
we'd be willing to serve
you with all our might.
What's going on?
What is Shen Gonghao up to now?
Finally, we're out! Yay!
Bye-bye!
Vile.
We're doomed.
How will we explain
this to General Li now?
Luckily no one saw us.
Here.
What for?
I'll break your arms
and then you break my legs.
We'll say the Yaksha did it.
Oh.
When the general sees
how badly we're hurt,
he won't blame us anymore.
Try your best.
Hit harder!
Hey!
Hey, you two!
Master Immortal,
you're here!
Hee hee hee!
Ha ha ha!
He let the Yaksha get away!
Huh?
It was all your fault.
Who are you to point fingers?
Who are you to play innocent?
Oh my,
Dumb and Dumber!
Hey!
You two boneheads!
Get over here and guard me!
Yes, Sir! Right away!
Show no mercy.
Shen Gongbao!
Ao Bing is not dead.
Chentang Pass and the dragons
have no reason to fight.
Taiyi is rebuilding Ao
Bing's body right now.
Liar!
Hmm?
The shield...
No!
Master!
Ao Bing!
Master Taiyi has
built me a new body.
Please, ceasefire.
Shen Gongbao,
I saved your disciple.
How will you thank me?
So,
that's Nezha in there?
Why, you ungrateful bastard!
Master!
They must die!
Ha ha ha!
You think you can
break this shield?
Hit me! Come on!
No!
This aura...
Ao Bing!
Father!
[Ao Guang]
I failed the mission
to save our kind.
No.
None of that matters.
I just want you to be safe.
As long as you're here,
it's enough for me.
Open Lotus!
Your body, what is...
Please, he's
literally a newborn.
How could he take
a hit like that?
Ao Bing!
Hey! it's not ready yet!
Don't move! Don't move!
Ao Bing, what's going on?
Never move before
your body's fixed.
If your body exceeds its limit,
it will collapse!
For heaven's sake...
Fatty!
Make another bod...
body for Ao Bing, now!
Huh?
Making two bodies back-to-back
has completely drained
the Sacred Lotus's energy.
Without a body, won't
his soul scatter?
Master, do something!
Without the Sacred Lotus,
there's nothing I can do.
It's okay.
I took your place as the
Spirit Pearl. I deserve this.
If my sacrifice
can bring you back to life,
then it's a fair price to pay.
Who asked you to?
Am happy being the Demon Orb.
Don't you dare die!
Father,
please spare Chentang Pass.
We should stop the mistakes.
This is my final wish.
There has to be other ways.
There has to be.
You! Try harder!
Let Ao Bing share
your body for now.
Share your body.
Two souls sharing one body,
rejection is inevitable.
The Spirit Pearl and Demon
Orb come from the same source.
Sharing one body
for seven days
shouldn't be a problem.
That's it!
Ao Bing, come on up!
Quick!
Okay.
This feels... strange...
Ao Bing, are you here?
Yes, I am.
I can hear your
voice in my head!
This is fun!
But this is only
a temporary fix.
What happens after seven days?
There's some potion in the vault
of Yu Xu Palace, Elixir Reparo.
It can restore the divine
power of magical items.
With it,
the Sacred Lotus
will bloom again.
But how will you obtain it?
I'll go to the Supreme Lord
himself and beg for it.
Or are you planning to
report on me and the dragons?
The Supreme Lord wouldn't sa...
save a son of the dragons.
If asking doesn't work,
then we'll just take it.
Yu Xu Palace is at the
core of the Chan Sect,
protected by formidable powers.
For my son,
I'll break into the Court
of Heaven if I have to.
Your Majesty, calm down.
I might have a plan.
Chan disciples who
excel in their training
can participate in
the Ascension Trial.
Passing the trial grants
not only immortality,
but also the right to choose one
ma... magic item from the
Yu Xu Vault as a reward.
Are you suggesting
Nezha participate in the trial
to obtain the elixir?
No, no, no!
He's beaming with
demonic energy!
As soon as he uses his
powers, he'll be exposed!
Isn't Ao Bing
sharing Nezha's body?
His divine aura can mask the
demonic energy perfectly.
As long as he passes the
trial within seven days,
not only will we have
the el... elixir...
But he can also
achieve immortality.
Then I'm not a demon anymore?
This will save both
Ao Bing and Nezha.
Eve... everyone is happy.
This isn't the
right thing to do.
Then what do you suggest?
Follow the rules.
Come clean with the Supreme Lord
and trust his judgement.
My wife and I will
also plead for mercy,
so the sins of the parents
don't affect the children.
Mere mortals,
you have only decades
of life experience,
how dare you lecture
me about morality?
Longer than I could remember,
I've lived for
thousands of years.
Let me tell you one
truth and one truth only.
If my son dies,
I'll have Chentang
Pass sink with him.
Stop!
Ao Bing is my friend.
I will save him for sure.
But if you dare to
harm Chentang Pass,
I'll smash your Dragon Palace
into P.I.E.C.E.S!
Except for Nezha and Taiyi,
no one leaves Chentang
Pass from now on.
If in seven days I
don't see Elixir Reparo,
or the news of my clan gets out,
I'll let Chentang Pass
sink forever.
I don't trust my siblings,
and I can't stay out
of my body for long.
The fate of Chentang Pass
is in your hands.
Yes.
Exactly.
There's no message
that can't be conveyed
with just a nod.
Lord Li,
we're all here to say goodbye
to Young Master Nezha.
We want to thank him for
saving the entire city.
You're too kind.
My son has caused enough trouble
over the years.
Always knew the Young Master
was destined for greatness.
Look at him,
a wide forehead,
broad face,
prominent nose,
full cheeks and thick lips.
All signs of a true hero!
I've never been wrong
in reading faces.
Young Master, remember to
brush your teeth after meals!
Boss!
The Demon Slayers is now
re-branded as the Nezha Gang.
All members will
follow your orders.
Young Master, want to
practice calligraphy?
I'm here for you!
Young Master, you're
three years old now.
It's time to get a girlfriend.
Any interests in instrument?
We're proficient in all of them.
I want to
play shuttlecock.
What?
It's fun.
Anyone?
I'll play with you.
Didn't you always want to
play shuttlecock with me?
Well...
he's a bit hard on the kicks.
Ha ha ha!
I'm a general of war!
Dad.
That's my boy!
How about...
we do it another day?
Nonsense!
Why stop when you're having fun?
It's fine. I'm fine.
I'll join too!
My lady, you don't
have to do this.
Are you looking down on me?
I'm also a general of war!
Nezha,
catch this!
Kiddo,
how did you miss that?
If only weren't the Demon Orb...
What was that?
Nothing.
It's time to go.
Before you go,
will you give your mother
a big hug?
Please, people are watching.
Wait.
Here are some snacks I made.
For you and your
master on the road.
Okay, okay.
We need to go.
Hey!
I'm not on board yet!
Your body isn't fully fixed.
Don't use too much force.
Alright, alright.
And watch your temper.
Try to stay calm out there.
Without me and your
father by your side,
learn to take care of yourself.
You silly child.
What's wrong with just a hug?
That's too cringey.
It's not a farewell anyway.
Let's move.
Why are you sighing?
Taste bad?
Food, food, food.
All you know is food.
Look at me,
I'm too worried to even eat!
Have you thought about
how to pass the trial?
What is the trial about?
It'll test the progress
of your cultivation.
In front of the judges,
you must defeat, barehanded,
three demon kings of
earth-monster level.
Fighting...
That's my specialty!
But as soon as you give
off demonic energy,
your identity will be exposed.
Just let Ao Bing
control my body.
His divine energy
will be just as powerful.
Sounds easy.
Let's try.
Nezha,
fully relax your body.
Let Ao Bing take
control and fight me.
Ao Bing, what are you doing?
Keep steady!
When a soul inhabits
another body,
unless your willpower is much
stronger than the host's,
you won't be able
to fully control it.
Nezha, step back.
The harder you push,
the less Ao Bing can control.
Use your leg!
Sweep him, sweep him!
Don't panic!
I'm coming...
for you.
Having fun, huh?
We're almost at Yu Xu Palace,
and you're still messing around.
Look at yourself,
what kind of mentor are you?
Stand here and reflect
on your mistakes.
No meals until
you figure it out!
You're a grown man.
Stop acting like a
reckless teenager.
I got it!
The Sleepy-Slumber Pill.
What's that?
Take this, and you'll
fall asleep immediately.
Once you're asleep,
Ao Bing can fully
control your body.
Brilliant!
One is enough!
Should've told me...
earlier.
Perfect.
Master Taiyi?
Now this feels
like the real deal.
What's wrong?
Don't worry.
I see you've completely
taken over Nezha's body.
Let's go again.
This time, I won't hold back.
You'd better give
it your all, too.
I humbly seek your guidance.
Not bad.
Barely able to match my skills.
Master Taiyi,
your nose is bleeding.
Too heaty recently.
Need more water.
No big deal.
Kunlun Mountain! We're here.
I heard a day here
equals a year in
the mortal world.
Don't worry.
We're not in the
celestial realm yet.
But this many people?
They've all come to
seek immortality.
Chan sect is famous
across the world,
and everyone wants to join.
Look at this.
The jasper.
It's a credential of
a Chan Sect immortal.
With it,
you'll receive respect
everywhere you go.
I'm telling ya.
Being an immortal is amazing.
Both of your brothers
have ascended.
You'll have no problem either.
I mean Nezha's brothers.
His two brothers
are among the best of the
third generation disciples.
You know,
how Nezha always
misbehaves, right?
So, I often tell stories
about his brothers
to set a good example for him.
Let me tell you something,
Nezha idolizes his brothers.
Oh wow, you're lucky
to meet the well-known
Demon Hunters.
Demon Hunters?
They roam the land, hunting down
demons that wreak
havoc on humanity,
keeping the world at peace.
The current leader
of the Demon Hunters
is the top disciple
of Immortal Wuliang.
Isn't his predecessor
Shen Gongbao?
[Yu Xu Palace]
Master Taiyi,
what's that smoke over there?
Oh.
That's the most precious
treasure of Yu Xu Palace.
The Tianyuan Cauldron.
Brother Taiyi.
[Immortal Wuliang]
It's been forever.
Brother Wuliang!
I heard that during
Master's seclusion,
you've been in charge
of Yu Xu Palace.
I've brought my disciple to
participate in the Ascension Trial.
Nezha,
Pay respect to Master Wuliang.
Master Wuliang.
So, you're Nezha?
The reincarnation
of the Spirit Pearl?
Oh my!
How remarkable!
The Supreme Lord holds
great expectations for you.
And you sure don't disappoint.
Look at him.
So full of robust vitality,
giving off a righteous vibe.
The boy's been over
training lately.
His state is a bit unstable.
What do you think you're doing?
This is Yu Xu Palace!
I need to pee!
Crana!
Here!
Take the child to
the restroom. [Crana]
Restroom?
I didn't say anything
about resting.
Idiot!
Restroom
is where you pee.
The boy's a bit rough.
Please forgive him.
Wow!
So white!
Is the entire
palace made of jade?
Where did they get so
much money to buy jade?
The "Yu" in Yu Xu Palace
means jade, right?
Then what does the "Xu" mean?
Humble?
Guilty?
Or emptiness?
Is the restroom
also made of jade?
Even immortals need to pee?
Does Immortal Wuliang also poop?
This is a place of cultivation.
Lower your voice.
How much further is the toilet?
I can't hold it anymore.
Hey, sister, wait for me!
You!
I didn't mean it.
I need to change my skirt.
Go by yourself.
But I don't know
where the toilet is.
Go through the corridor,
turn right, then left.
Oh.
Wow.
How fancy it is!
Radical!
Weird.
Am I lost?
Where are you going?
Oh.
I got lost.
Follow me.
Brother, good job
raising the Spirit Pearl.
Another great
achievement for the Sect.
Not at all.
It's all thanks to
Master's guidance.
This Kunlun Dew
is a rare elixir.
Normally, it takes six
months to fill a basin.
But today, when I
sent someone to check,
it's already full!
Your timing couldn't be better.
Brother,
luck sure favors
you, doesn't it?
What's wrong with you?
Can't even drink water properly.
My disciple is a bit crude.
Please forgive him.
My pee is in the water.
My master is a bit crude, too.
Please forgive him.
Brother,
time is of the essence.
I think Nezha should go
through the trial immediately.
Why the rush?
Let's have a few
more drinks first.
No, no thank you.
Alright, then.
My disciple Deero
will be the judge.
The next target of
the Demon Hunters
can be captured by Nezha.
Brother, excuse us.
Taiyi, my brother,
always so impatient.
The taste of the Dew this year
is especially rich.
Keep using this
method in the future.
Yes, master.
Why stop?
It's been six hours,
Master Shen.
Too tired to continue.
Rubbish!
Cultivation allows no laziness.
Without my permission
you'll never stop.
General Li Jing of Chentang
Pass is here to see you.
Master Shen,
yesterday's battle
left many soldiers and civilians
of Chentang Pass injured.
We've run out of medicine.
Humbly ask you to open a path
so that a few doctors can
leave the city to buy supplies.
How bold!
No wonder you're...
Who did that?
You son of a...
I...
St... stop, stop, stop!
Bring me the one
you caught earlier.
He escaped the city
during the battle.
General Li, please,
take him ba... back with you.
This is a misunderstanding,
Master Shen!
I'm a demon too!
I captured this Yaksha
to clear my son's name.
Now that it's settled,
and since he hasn't
done anything worse,
just let him go.
Yes, exactly.
I'm just a small role.
Insignificant.
I don't think you understood me.
No one leaves here,
not even a demon.
Let alone humans.
Master Shen, please have mercy.
I'm a demon, too.
We are both villains!
Pfft!
I'm n... not a villain.
Everyone who knows the
secret of the Spirit Pearl
must stay here.
Without medicine,
the injured won't survive.
Master Shen, please,
I'm only asking to save lives.
Sir!
We caught a spy.
This creature came
from outside the city,
and injured some
of our soldiers.
Lock... lock him up too.
Brother.
Brother, is that you?
You...
Brother, it's me!
[Shen Xiaobao]
Xiaobao?
You haven't been
home for centuries.
I miss you so much.
What are you doing here?
Father sent me to find you.
Look,
the compass you gave me.
It tells me where you are.
Father,
how is he doing?
He's great.
Ever since you
entered Yu Xu Palace,
father's been full of energy,
like he took some miracle tonic.
You are the only one
from our village ever
to make it as a
Chan Sect immortal.
Now, fellow demons
from miles around
are pouring in to
train with father.
By the way,
why are you here?
Didn't you promise me before,
once I've achieved human form,
you'd get me into Yu Xu Palace?
Look! can turn into a human now!
All these years,
I've trained so hard,
and never slacked off.
You're my role
model, big brother.
Glory to Yu Xu,
answering heaven's call.
Travel the world,
bringing justice to all.
Say, brother,
what are you doing here?
I... I...
Are these sea monsters
your subordinates?
Why are you surrounding
Chentang Pass?
Well, about that...
Th... this is...
Master Shen is
defending Chentang Pass.
Huh?
Evil forces invaded the city.
Master Shen and the sea
clan came to our aid.
On behalf of my people,
thank you for this noble act.
Don't mention it.
Wow!
Brother, you're incredible!
Is this the demon
attacking Chentang Pass?
Ah!
You are a disgrace
to all demons!
Shame on you!
Hey,
Xiaobao,
can you
wait a few more years
before going to Yu Xu Palace?
Huh?
Why?
I can transform
into a human now!
It's just that...
I'm preparing for my promotion
to the Twelve Golden Immortals,
so I can't be distracted.
Twelve Golden Immortals?
Once it's done,
I'll take you there,
okay?
No problem, brother!
Your promotion is
more important.
Can go to Yu Xu Palace anytime.
Besides,
haven't quite mastered
the shape-shifting.
I'll go back and practice more.
Practice more.
Xiaobao,
this is what I saved up
since entering the Palace.
What is it?
Yu Xu Palace gives all disciples
these immortality pills.
Take one
and you ga... gain ten
years' worth of cultivation.
But...
this is too precious.
Brother, you're training
for a promotion.
You should keep them.
I don't like how it tastes.
I prefer cultivating my own.
You... you bring them back.
Share with the family.
No, I can't.
Father will blame me.
Xiaobao,
are you not obeying
your big brother?
Take the pills and leave now.
This is the front line.
If... if you stay,
I'll be distracted.
Then...
I...
I'll leave.
Brother.
You must make it into the
Twelve Golden Immortals.
I'll keep training myself.
I appreciate your help,
but the stake is too high
for me to let anyone through.
This Yaksha...
you... you bring him back, too.
I wasn't helping you.
I was helping the young one.
A good role model
can change his life.
Wait.
Le... leave me a list
of medicines you need.
[Level 1 Bandits Hill]
Am Nezha, the Third Prince bold.
I slay the demons, I
write in rhyme untold.
Today I come to rid
the evil's breath.
You wicked fiends,
prepare for death!
Still eating?
You are doomed.
Ahhh!
Who do you think you are?
Barging into our Bandits Hill?
So you're in charge?
Come forward
and have a taste of my power.
You arrogant spoilt brat.
Boss,
teach him a lesson.
Show me what got.
You go.
No, but, boss...
how dare I steal your thunder?
Fighting a child is
just embarrassing.
When I say go, you go.
Hey, k-k-kid.
Since you're young and naive,
I'm willing to let this slide.
You, you...
It's still not too late
to run home to mommy.
What's wrong?
Why are you awake again?
I don't know.
I'm a light sleeper.
All that shaking
has jolted me awake.
Damn it.
He took too much of that pill
and now he's immune.
Increase the dose then.
If you insist to stay,
you might get hurt.
I was going to
dodge to the right.
Sorry, I thought it was left.
So weak.
Master Taiyi.
Maybe I should cut in.
He could use a few
more years' training.
Not so fast.
He was just teasing the demon.
The boy likes to...
play dumb.
Pills.
I need pills.
I gave you a warning.
Now you know who
you're messing with.
Oh no!
The pills have
dissolved in the soup!
Then I'll drink the soup.
And you're trying
to steal our soup?
This calls for a beating.
So gross.
Super Mighty Club Strike!
See!
I told you he was pretending.
I wasn't paying attention.
Not possible!
You suck!
Step aside!
Watch me kick his butt.
Why did you spit it all out?
The taste is too strong.
I couldn't help it.
Check this out!
Funny!
This isn't working.
We can't win without the pill.
Deero is watching.
I can't give you the pill.
What do we do now?
I got it.
There is another way.
You're not suggesting...
We can eat the puke.
But,
it's disgusting.
What's the big deal?
I've drank Yaksha booger before.
This explains a lot.
No pain,
no gain.
That's how Nezha defeat fate.
The lives of my parents
and friends are at stake,
and the people of
Chentang Pass too.
This is E-A-S-Y P-E-A-S-Y!
With ignoring prejudice,
and overcoming inner fears,
I will change my destiny.
I've kept low-key
until today's show.
Master Taiyi...
I'll save Nezha first.
Then we'll figure out a
way for Elixir Reparo.
No way.
I don't believe this.
Kid,
let's go another round.
Fake death?
I'I smash you!
Good thing Nezha
got knocked out.
You do suck!
Let me avenge you!
Invincible Whirlwind Punch!
Ahhh!
Do we have to catch them all?
Even leaving one behind
could harm the people here.
Take them all back
to Yu Xu Palace.
The Sect will guide
them to the right path,
turning evil to good.
Your face...
No biggy.
He's sometimes ugly,
sometimes handsome.
Spirit Pearl, you know,
not like normal people.
Be more careful next time.
You scared my soul out.
Who's this kid?
Nezha, possibly.
Jinzha and Muzha's
younger brother.
He's the Spirit Pearl reincarnation
appointed by the Supreme Lord.
But his looks aren't much, huh?
Hunched back.
Wobbly pace.
Sinking brows and drooping eyes.
Rude face.
Not to mention the
dark eye circles.
He's like a ghost.
Don't stir up trouble now.
Brother,
what's the star sign tonight?
Six stars in alignment,
once in a decade.
Whenever six stars align,
this Jade Podium can transmit sound
and images across thousands of miles.
Our brothers scatter
all over the world.
And finally get together.
Tonight is the night,
the Golden Immortals shall meet.
I haven't ascended
to the Twelve yet.
Maybe I shouldn't be included.
It's only a matter of time.
No la, no la.
It's not appropriate at all.
I can't do it, really.
Then why are you
sitting up there?
Shut up!
Would it kill you to
see your master thrive?
A sauna!
Shh!
Brothers and sisters, I humbly
welcome you back to your places.
Greetings, Brother Wuliang!
Allow me to introduce
a new member.
Brother Taiyi.
He has fulfilled the
master's expectations.
And successfully nurtured
the Spirit Pearl reincarnation.
Pay your respect.
The Deification War is imminent.
We are here to discuss
the preparation.
Chan Sect is the orthodox of
Tao, [Immortal Guangcheng]
so we're destined to win.
[Immortal Guangcheng]
So we're destined to win.
But as Jie Sect has risen rapidly
these years, [Immortal Chijing]
we must remain vigilant.
[Immortal Chijing]
[Immortal Ju Liu Sun]
Jie sect, [Immortal Ju Liu Sun]
is where furry and horny beasts
gather [Immortal Ju Liu Sun]
is where furry and
horny beasts gather
and creatures born
of mucus and eggs.
This war concerns the
survival of our sect.
We must be careful.
[Immortal Huanglong]
Strengthening our power
is the key. [Immortal Huanglong]
Is the key.
Precisely,
That's why I began
preparing early.
Immortality pills,
a total of nine thousand,
could be allocated
according to grades.
This will definitely
boost our strength.
How are there so many?
[Immortal Daoheng]
For a hundred years,
our master has tirelessly refined
pills with the Tianyuan Cauldron,
working day and night,
at the cost of his
own cultivating.
Brother Wuliang has dedicated himself
to building our sect, [Immortal Lingbao]
his contributions
are to be praised.
Aye, aye.
Besides the Jie Sect,
[Immortal Cihang]
are there other evil forces plotting
against us? [Immortal Cihang]
Are there other evil
forces plotting against us?
Master Cihang,
as soon as menacing
demons are discovered,
the Demon Hunters will
immediately be sent out.
So, most stray demons
post no threat.
But,
there is one exception.
Oh? [Immortal Yuding]
Who is that? [Immortal Yuding]
The Eastern Sea dragons.
Dragons?
Didn't they surrender to the Court
of Heaven long ago? [Immortal Qingxu]
No kind could be trusted
except for our own.
To me,
their surrender is
merely a facade,
hibernating for a moment.
The dragons have helped subdue the
abyss monsters for thousands of years.
What's their crime?
But they own great strength.
If they betray us in the war,
the whole situation
could be overturned.
But we still can't do that.
Our reputation of righteousness
and justness is known to all.
[Immortal Wenshu] Our reputation of
righteousness and justness is known to all.
If we gratuitously
[Immortal Wenshu]
attack the surrendered,
How will anyone ever trust us?
Aye.
We must not act rashly.
Further deliberation
is necessary.
But...
Enough.
They made their points.
And you don't have
to be bigoted.
OK.
The time of the six-star
alignment is almost over.
Since there are no other topics,
let's adjourn the meeting.
Brother,
Jinzha and Muzha,
are disciples of myself
and Brother Puxian.
They have been cultivating here
for many years away from home,
and have never even met Nezha,
their younger brother.
[Immortal Puxian] Since there's still
time left in the six-star alignment,
why not let them
[Immortal Puxian]
meet for awhile?
Great idea.
OMG!
What should I do?
What's wrong?
. Speaking of my look...
Will my first impression...
be bad?
Of course not!
Really?
Though slovenly,
you've got strong will.
Though short,
you've got a big heart.
Though ugly,
you're kind inside.
Though you have
black eye circles,
a piggy nose,
and a missing tooth,
I still think
you're truly incredibly great.
And I'm sure your
brothers would agree.
Thanks for the compliment.
What are you doing?
You go meet my brothers for me.
Seriously?
How can I do this for you?
No, Nezha.
Nezha!
The boy is a bit shy.
Brother!
Ao Bing,
you cried?
This reminded me
of my two brothers.
You have brothers too?
Mmm.
I used to.
Having two such
wonderful brothers.
You're so lucky.
What were you talking
about just now?
They said
they're sorry for not checking
on you all these years.
They asked
how things have been at home,
if your parents are well,
what hobbies you have,
and who your friends are.
They also said
whatever problems you may have in
the future, you must tell them.
And remember, you
have two brothers
who will always, always
help and protect you.
Why are you...
Nothing.
It's just eyes in my sand.
You sure it's not
the other way around?
Annoying!
I already said it's nothing.
OK. You are the boss here.
I'm not talking to you.
Fine fine,
I'll stop laughing.
Are you still mad?
Nezha?
Nezha!
Ao Bing,
I've been violent and
unruly since I was young,
making my parents worry all day.
Your father,
though he attacked
Chentang Pass,
I know he only risked everything
for your sake.
And today,
my brothers were so kind to me.
Our families have
sacrificed so much for us.
You're a monster,
and I'm a demon.
We're both burdens
for our families.
So what if we were
born as demons?
Immortal or demon,
I make the choice.
Once you're saved,
we must win ourselves a
place among the immortals
so our families won't
have to worry anymore.
Yes!
Only by becoming immortals,
can we have everyone's respect.
Deal!
I'm going to become an immortal!
Only with courage and diligence
can great progress be made.
[Level 2 Ascension Falls] Only with courage
and diligence can great progress be made.
At this speed, cultivating
[Level 2 Ascension Falls]
a hundred more years
would still be in vain.
About cultivating,
the priorities are vitality,
energy, and spirit.
If you feel it's difficult,
or you feel exhausted,
it's because you
were born demons.
Only by giving it your all
will you have a chance
to change your destiny
and achieve immortality.
Life or death, of
none I'm scared,
defying authority is
what I've revered.
My fate is mine,
not heaven's plan.
This bad boy will
become a godly man!
Bravo!
Just a few lines,
yet so powerful,
truly inspiring.
A great poem, indeed.
This is something all of
you should learn from.
Really?
Is it that good?
I just made it up.
It is good.
Every word counts,
and it's inspiring.
A poem like this
shows the ambition
of you, young man.
A true young hero
with a bright future ahead!
Oh, come on. It's just fine.
Actually, it still
has some tiny flaws.
More like plenty of flaws.
Let me ask you,
what's with those
dark eye circles?
It's obvious you stay
up late all the time.
Your life is undisciplined,
your diet unhealthy,
and you can't even manage
basic self-control.
How dare you dream of
becoming an immortal?
I was born with
dark eye circles.
Appearance reflects the
heart, don't you know?
Take a look at
yourself in the mirror.
Ridiculous, reckless and sloppy.
If you were my disciple, I'd
make you rebuild your human form.
Can be rebuilt?
Then there's hope
for my looks, right?
Teach me, please.
Knew you came to find
yourself a master.
Listen, kid,
I see you have great ambition,
so I'll take you as my disciple.
Cool!
Master!
Come,
train with your brothers.
Train for what?
Immortality, of course.
I don't need you
to teach me that.
Teach me how to be prettier.
Ridiculous!
You're putting looks
before cultivation?
Get your priorities straight.
Are you teaching me or not?
We're no longer
master and disciple.
You deserve to have
panda eyes for life.
That's too much.
I was going to go easy on you!
What's this?
Are you challenging me?
Three pills should be enough.
Kid,
go back where you came from.
If you keep
disrupting our class,
this could end badly for you.
Apologies.
You're no match for me.
Impressive, kid.
I underestimated you.
Try this!
Yeah, teach this
ignorant brat a lesson.
Master will surely win!
So fast!
You saw it?
We have no grudges between us.
You'd better go.
I cannot lose.
You can't even touch me.
Let alone fight.
Smart move!
Hold him tight, render
his speed useless.
Surrender?
Wait, you are...
Finally figured it out?
It's not that I'm fast,
I just transform into
electric currents,
traveling instantly
to any location.
In water,
I am invincible!
Impressive cryo power.
Stay calm.
Go too hard and your
body will collapse!
Ice doesn't conduct electricity.
Let's see what else you've got.
Lakes and seas. Clouds and sky.
By this divine talisman in my hand.
Wind is to rise and rain is to fall.
Swift and Uplift!
Father!
Damn it.
The Rain Summoning Spell.
End this now!
Too late.
You're doomed.
Master!
Master, are you all right?
I wasn't going to
take your life.
You didn't have to
sacrifice an arm.
All disciples, listen.
Take the demons
back to the palace.
Yes!
Stop!
Put them down.
All of you, put them down!
May I ask if you are a
member of the Chan Sect?
That's correct.
Ah.
These are all immortals
from Yu Xu Palace.
You must not be disrespectful.
Entering Yu Xu Palace
and receiving the teachings
of the righteous path
may not be a bad thing.
All of you, drop your weapons!
Father!
Xiaobao?
How come you're back?
Xiaobao,
stand down!
Xiaobao!
Impudent!
How dare you hurt
our Sect members?
No!
Father!
Nezha,
freeze the river now!
You can't escape!
Father!
Go!
Go now!
Run!
Father...
There's no escape.
Step aside.
He's just trying
to save his father.
You didn't have to be so brutal.
Hmph.
Panax notoginseng,
cattail pollen,
munjeet,
borneol,
dragon's blood.
One more basket.
Safflower,
angelica,
pseudo-ginseng powder,
sappanwood,
poison nut.
My lord,
we now have everything
on the list,
along with a hundred extra
baskets of sea products.
We happen to be short on
food supplies in the city.
Master Shen, a moment, please.
We've prepared a meal.
Would you honor us
with your presence?
You...
Thanks to Lord Li's kindness,
I've been taken in as a servant.
He may be a demon,
but he has a good heart.
As long as he behaves,
there's no reason he
can't have a future.
Wonder if the dishes
suit your taste.
Not...
Not bad.
Then have some more.
Try this liquor as well.
I quit long ago.
Cultivators must sup...
suppress desires.
As the saying goes,
one must cut off urges
to perfect the spirit.
Another saying goes,
one must practice
kindness to polish virtue.
Talking won't help.
I've already re... reached
the point of no return.
You can't hide forever.
The truth will come out one day.
If you continue to harm lives
making more mistakes,
even if you can
deceive everyone,
you won't be able
to fool yourself.
And you will not improve
further on your cultivation,
the essence of which
is doing good deeds and
walking the righteous path.
Enough!
What nonsense!
You know nothing
about cultivation.
Sir!
Someone is here to
see Master Shen.
Brother
Who did this to you?
Some Taoists.
They attacked us.
Father...
had one of his arms
cut off.
Who did it?
His name is...
Ne...
Zha.
Congratulations on
passing Level 2.
Please inform Brother Wuliang.
Master is in seclusion
refining pills
and has not emerged yet.
Before Level 3,
why don't you rest
for a few days?
We only have two days left.
No need.
I'm so fine.
Let's continue the test.
Well,
as you wish.
The final test
is the demon Queen
of Skull Mountain,
Shi Ji.
Someone is requesting an urgent
meeting with Master Taiyi.
Huh?
Please help us!
It's Chentang Pass.
Something happened!
Dad.
Mom.
Dad?
Mom?
Dad!
Mom!
Calm down.
Let's keep looking.
Keep looking.
I received an urgent report
as soon as I ended seclusion.
Who could have committed
such a horrendous crime?
Master,
according to Shieldos,
they were struck by
a tremendous force
and lost consciousness.
When they woke up,
people of Chentang Pass had
already been slaughtered.
We haven't obtained
the elixir yet.
Why would they do that?
Brother,
any clue?
No, no.
Was just thinking,
where did all this
lava come from?
Exactly.
There are no volcanoes for
hundreds of miles around.
This is truly bizarre.
Everyone, come quick!
What demon is this?
This is...
left by a dragon's claw.
Impossible!
The dragons are
all in Eastern Sea,
guarding the Suppression Seal.
Not a single one
could have left.
Master,
if I remember correctly,
Queen Ao Run of Western Sea
has a special skill
called the Sky...
Sky-Splitting Claw.
Are you saying she used
the Sky-Splitting Claw
to cross into Chentang Pass?
That explains the lava.
It must have been transported
from the purgatory remotely.
But she's watched by the
Dragon King of Eastern Sea.
It's impossible for
her to cross over.
Then there's only
one possibility left.
The thing I worried the most
happened.
The King of Eastern
Sea has betrayed us?
This is too serious
an accusation.
Could we be wrong?
No.
It's them!
What are you doing?
Don't be impulsive.
Are you heading to
the Dragon Palace?
That's the direction
of Skull Mountain.
The dragons slaughtered
innocent civilians,
committing this
unforgivable atrocity.
No need to consult with
fellow Golden Immortals.
I'll strike first
and explain later.
Crana,
back to the palace with me.
Summon all the Demon Hunters.
Roger.
Brother,
Nezha's parents were
killed by demons.
We can't let anything
happen to the child.
Go with Deero for him now.
Yes.
I know you're
heartbroken right now
but can you please
calm down for a moment?
Can you
take me to the
Dragon Palace first?
I'll confront my
father and master
to get to the bottom of this.
Will that bring my parents back?
[Level 3 Skull Mountain]
Mirror mirror on the wall,
who's the fairest within
ten miles and more?
It's you, my lady.
[Lady Shi Ji]
And who is the fairest within
a hundred miles? [Lady Shi Ji]
And who is the fairest
within a hundred miles?
It's you, my lady.
What about a thousand miles?
It's you.
And ten thousand miles?
And in the whole world?
Still you.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Lie better, at least.
No, no.
I was just trying
not to piss you off.
You know what?
Telling the truth
won't hake me mad.
Seriously?
I, Lady Shi Ji, am
indeed a stumning beauty,
but I know there's
always someone better.
Go on and ask then.
Am I the fairest of them all?
No.
Fair enough.
Am The fairest within
ten thousand miles?
No.
What about a thousand miles?
Hundred miles?
No.
Ten miles?
Nope.
Am I even the fairest
on this mountain?
Nope.
Screw you!
There isn't any other
female in this mountain.
I'm female, too.
You promised you won't get mad.
You are prettier than me?
Help!
How the hell!
Demon, show yourself!
Who are you calling demon?
It's Lady Shi Ji.
Damn kid.
Have we even met?
What the hell are you up to?
You will be exposed.
Let me.
Stay out of it.
You think you can defeat me?
The entire mountain is my body.
I'll see how you can destroy me.
If you use more force,
your body will collapse!
I said
stay out of it!
Already started!
Crap!
I'm so screwed.
Luckily there's some left.
I shall live to
fight another day.
Damn kid.
Just you wait.
Nine-Dragon Fire Trap!
No escape!
Oh my!
Reckless child.
You body has almost gone.
Are you trying to kill yourself?
What's that fire earlier?
Isn't Nezha
a frost mage?
Who... who said that?
Frost, flame, I taught it all.
His powers are...
a combination of ice and fire.
Is that possible?
The Spirit Pearl is endowed
with unparalleled talents.
Can't judge him by
normal standards.
Which one of us is the teacher?
You think you know
better than me?
I wouldn't dare.
However,
I did sense a strong presence
of demonic energy earlier
About that...
Shi Ji must have released it.
What are you saying, fatty?
I did not...
Was it you? Was it
you? Was it you?
Say it!
It was me, it was me!
Stop shaking!
I'm about to throw up!
See? I told you.
Nezha,
you've passed three levels.
Today,
I will personally cast
the Ascension Spell for you.
I've been through all
of this long long ago.
I was probably too nervous.
The Ascension Spell is
longer than I remember.
From now on,
you're an Immortal
of the Chan Sect.
This Yu Xu Treasure Vault
houses all sorts of
rare magic items.
Elixir Reparo.
You can only pick one.
Don't you need more
time to decide?
Elixir Reparo.
Yu Xu Palace has sent messengers
to inform the Twelve about
what the dragons did.
However, due to
the great distance,
my brothers and sisters
can't make it here sooner.
[Tianyuan Cauldron] my brothers and
sisters can't make it here sooner.
This time, [Tianyuan Cauldron]
I will personally lead the
hunt [Tianyuan Cauldron]
on the dragons.
[Tianyuan Cauldron]
On the dragons.
Nezha,
I will you fight alongside me?
Let me go back to
Chentang Pass first.
Then we'll seek revenge
on the Dragon King.
OK.
With your extraordinary
combat skills,
you'd be a great help in
destroying the Dragon Palace.
I've paid back
everything I owed you.
Wait.
Wait until my body is restored.
Let's go to the Dragon
Palace together, okay?
You know well what
I'm going to do.
You being there will
only make it harder.
Next time we meet,
we're foes instead of friends.
Ugh...
Karma it is.
No, you can't leave!
Your soul will scatter before
you get to the Dragon Palace.
Nine-Dragon Fire Trap!
Calm down, will you?
Going now
won't change anything.
Leave me alone.
I promised Nezha I'd
save you no matter what.
Pah! Pah!
Suffocating!
[Relic of Dragon Palace]
Who's there?
I'm Immortal Wuliang
of the Chan Sect.
Ao Guang,
do you admit your guilt?
So,
you've found out?
Is
Ao Bing still alive?
I'll accept whatever
punishment you give,
but please spare my son.
Nonsense!
The Court of Heaven ordered your
clan to suppress the sea monsters.
Instead, you colluded with them
and slaughtered Chentang Pass.
Chentang Pass?
The dragons have committed
an unforgivable crime.
Today,
justice shall be meted.
Encompassed are the
earth and the skies.
Unleash the power
with boundless might.
Let the Tianyuan
rise and stand tall.
Reign supreme above them all.
Open Cauldron!
Show yourselves!
What have you done
to Chentang Pass?
Didn't big brother tell us
to follow Master Shen's orders?
Shen Gongbao?!
Speaking of the emergency,
you should focus on present.
My king,
we can't sit here
and wait to die!
If I go into battle,
the Suppression Seal will...
Leave that to us.
Joining all our powers,
we can hold it for long enough.
Fine.
I've had enough!
You wretched demon!
This is a once-in-a-millennium
chance for revenge.
Break out of the purgatory!
Destroy the Dragon Palace!
Soul Blade!
Old fool!
Taste my sword!
Releasing demonic
energy like this...
aren't you afraid of
exposing your identity?
I told you,
if you dared to
harm Chentang Pass,
would smash your
palace into PIECES!
Tell me!
Is Ao Bing dead?
Move! Out of my way!
Rise!
Do you have a death wish?
Let's see how long
your body can take it.
I don't care if I live or die.
As long as you're dead!
Now is the time!
Look what you've done!
Is annihilation for all
really what you want?
The chains.
Even the Eastern Sea Dragon
King can't match your power.
I was right after all.
You're exactly what
the Chan Sect needs.
Your parents spent their
lives fighting evil.
From now on,
you must carry on their legacy
and eliminate all the demons.
Let me avenge your loss
by turning these
bastards into pills.
Escort me!
Yes, master!
Nezha!
Dad!
Mom!
Nezha!
Son, are you alright?
Your body...
I... I...
They already know
about you and Ao Bing.
I... I...
I thought...
I'd never see you again.
Master is still
casting the spell.
We need to buy as
much time as we can.
Nezha,
it wasn't my father who
slaughtered Chentang Pass.
The real culprit
is him, the Immortal Wuliang!
Shieldos!
Dragons?
Brother,
it's been a while.
Why are you here?
Shen Gongbao,
you collude with the dragons.
What are you up to?
Should be ask... asking you.
You captured my father.
What are you up to?
Who said I captured your father?
Only you know my
family's situation.
If you didn't give the order,
why would Nezha and the Demon
Hunters hunt my father down?
And my little brother's
arrow wound...
It's obviously
caused by your disciple, Deero!
There's the talent
I recruited myself.
Nothing slips past you.
After all, I've done your
dirty work for so many years.
I can also guess
your purpose here
putting up a show
in Chentang Pass.
You are trying to fram...
frame the dragons, aren't you?
Is this how you repay me,
your brother and mentor?
You've always use...
used me for your benefit.
Between you and me,
there's only grudge,
not gratitude.
May I interest you in a deal?
Master Immortal.
As the overseer of Yu Xu Palace,
you must know the spell to unhinge
the Sea-Stabilizing Chains.
I do.
So what?
You... you are going to rebel?
A thousand years ago, the four of us
fought the celestial realm together.
Who has then betrayed us and
cast us into the purgatory?
Now Wuliang is
targeting Ao Guang,
that's exactly what we want.
I've long heard that Immortal
Wuliang recruit talents without bias.
I trust it you know
well what we can do.
If you can free us
from the purgatory
and help us achieve immortality,
we are willing to offer
our humble service.
Plus the secret of the Spirit
Pearl and the Demon Orb.
The Spirit Pearl
and the Demon Orb?
Pathetic!
Whe... where's your
spirit of fighting back?
We were young and ignorant!
A thousand years of imprisonment
has taught us about the rules
and the rulers.
Smart.
But you're so unpredictable.
How can I trust you?
Unless you let me
place on you...
We are willing.
The three dragons
willingly agreed
to let Wuliang place
a curse on them.
If they dare to
disobey in the future,
Wuliang can take their
lives at any time.
Wuliang then
fulfilled his promise,
freeing them from the
Sea-Stabilizing Chains.
Whenever a powerful
force is discovered,
he orchestrates massacres,
frames them,
and sends troops
to capture them.
According to Shen Gongbao,
he had carried out many
such tasks for Wuliang
in exchange for a chance
to join the Chan Sect.
This time, Wuliang came
to destroy Chentang Pass
and frame the dragons
of Eastern Sea.
One thing led to another,
he ended up recruiting
the three dragon kings.
And from them,
he learned the secret of the
Demon Orb and the Spirit Pearl.
After that,
they deliberately left
two clueless survivors
to tell Yu Xu Palace
what happened.
Seeing no hope of
breaking through,
Shen Gongbao came
up with a plan.
He had the Yaksha petrify us,
then hide us in the sewers.
Later, he waited for the
right time to revive us.
And you?
My families are gone.
I have nothing
left to hold onto.
Over there!
The demons captured
by the Demon Hunters
are not, as outsiders think,
being reformed in Yu Xu Palace.
Instead, they are thrown into
the Tianyuan Cauldron by Wuliang,
refined into pills
of immortality
to strengthen the
Chan Sect's power.
Brother,
how could you commit
such atrocities?
How...
How are you going
to face our master
and the teachings we received?
Now that you know
what Wuliang did,
you should stop
before it's too late.
Take him back to the palace
to face punishment
from the Supreme Lord.
The Demon Hunters were personally
trained by Master Wuliang.
Do you think a few words
would turn us against him?
So,
I was wrong about the dragons.
Let them go!
Let me help.
You betrayed us?
We learned that from
you, Big Brother.
Back then, in order
to protect our kind,
I had no choice!
Well, in order to
protect myself now,
Neither do I.
My King, wait for us!
Don't leave us behind!
My King, take us with you!
My King! My King!
You've all been sold out!
Dragon King of Southern Sea.
Dragon King of Northern Sea.
Queen of Western Sea.
[Ao Qin, Ao Run, Ao Shun]
Nephew,
it's playtime with
your second uncle.
Take my spear!
Take my axe!
Take my wheel!
Take my wheel times a hundred!
Two hundreds!
Three hundreds!
Enough, huh?
Bullshit!
There weren't that many.
Your body is still unstable.
Don't exhaust yourself.
For my mistakes,
I would give my life
for freeing the dragons.
Young and vicious.
Let me have some fun
with you, little one.
Bullying children,
shameless and vile!
Hey!
How dare you hit your
master's brother!
Bullying an uncle,
eat a knuckle!
This won't do.
It's a mess.
Then let's make it messier.
How about some vapor?
Sure.
Take them down!
Watch out for sneak attacks.
There you are.
Careful, it's me!
Brother?
Sorry, sorry.
Nezha!
Ah!
Surprise!
LOL!
Transformation Spell?
Are you insane?
You can't fool me.
Huh?
Which one of you...
Code.
She sells seashells
by the seashore.
What?
You don't know the code.
Imposter!
So you really are an imposter!
Unbelievable!
Serves you right.
Huh?
Code.
Eh... he sells bells
in the big well?
Wrong!
It's "she sells seashells
by the seashore"
and the shells she sells
all smell for sure”.
I'm the real one!
How come I don't know this code?
We just made it up!
Can't you make it easier?
It's too hard!
You idiot!
Go away!
Imposter!
I'm the real Ao Shun!
Crap! You don't know the code!
Neither do you!
That's true.
Does it mean I'm
an imposter, too?
My goodness.
Tai Chi flows in harmony divine.
Five elements perfectly align.
True fire of Samadhi
ignites the gold.
A perfect pill,
its power unfolds.
Swift and Uplift!
Why are you so scared?
We used to bathe in
lava like it's nothing.
Hot! Hot!
Oh no!
It's the true fire of Samadhi.
What are you looking at?
If anyone should
eat this, it's me!
Yum.
Let go of my father!
Hyah!
Freeze!
What a Spirit Pearl!
Perfect match with
the Demon Orb.
Ao Bing!
Hyah!
Freeze!
Ah!
The Heart-Piercing Curse.
Since I already knew
your true identities,
how could not have
a backup plan?
Impossible.
That curse is quite complex.
When did you cast it?
Oh...
That's why the Ascension
Spell took so long.
You slipped in something.
You old fart!
Even the Demon Orb
won't be able to break the
Heart-Piercing Curse so quick.
A thousand spikes have pierced
through your nerves and veins.
Forcing any movement
will only result in your body
being torn apart.
No wonder I couldn't
sense any living aura.
You were petrified.
But you staying alive
only harms Nezha.
The Spirit Pearl
and the Demon Orb
are precious treasures.
I wanted to treat you well,
but now you'll just
serve as pills.
Ao Bing!
Father!
You...
you're still alive!
Ungh!
It's the Heart-Piercing
Curse casted by Wuliang.
And he was the one that slaughtered
Chentang Pass, framing it on the dragons.
Father,
Nezha was deceived.
Don't blame him.
Whatever you want
to do, do it to me.
Leave my parents out of this.
Killing you won't
change anything.
We're all doomed to die here.
If anyone still holds grudges,
be my guest.
Brother,
the Chan Sect has
a noble reputation,
how could you commit
such a horrible offense?
Don't make more mistakes!
Why don't you go back
and confess to Master?
I'll plead for mercy
on your behalf.
You...
Indiscriminate fool!
Should the immortals' place
in the world be secured,
or you ungrateful
slackers are half as
diligent as the demons,
I wouldn't have wasted
this much time and effort!
Even if it leads to my own doom
and infamy,
I did it for the eternal
dominance of Chan Sect.
My conscience...
conscience...
My conscience is clear.
Another one is done.
I can't possibly eat any more.
You should try some.
Thanks.
When my fins are done,
you should try some too.
The claws are ready as well.
We should swap and share.
What's going on?
My body...
He's become a pill!
I'm still so young.
Don't want to die.
No, let me out.
Help!
Stay calm!
Focus all your energy!
Hold on for as long as you can.
Son!
Your power is greater than mine.
You can get through.
If you can hold out until the
Heart-Piercing Curse fades,
you'll have a chance to escape.
The Heart-Piercing Curse
takes at least six hours.
I'm afraid...
I won't be able
to last that long.
My lady.
Mom!
Wake up, mom.
Nezha, Nezha?
Nezha.
I'm here, Mom.
You and Dad must not give up.
Don't worry about us.
Try to
stay focused.
I'm fine, Mom.
I don't feel the fire.
Nothing kills you, kiddo.
If I am correct,
flames of the Demon Orb and
the true fire of Samadhi
share the same origin.
Then the Tianyuan
Cauldron can't harm you.
That's right.
My mistake.
Don't bother.
This is just my avatar.
As suspected, the Demon Orb
is indestructible.
No wonder the Supreme Lord had to
destroy you with the Wrath of Heaven.
Nezha,
I see you're a good son.
How about I give you a
chance to prove that?
The Oblivion Pill.
Swallow it
and I'll release your parents.
What do you say?
I may be ruthless,
but I always keep my promises.
Otherwise, all those
elites of the demons
wouldn't swear loyalty to me.
As long as you swallow it,
I swear to Heaven,
I won't harm your parents.
What are you doing?
Using his parents'
lives to threaten a kid?
And you call yourself a god?
You aren't even
worthy to be a human.
Nezha,
leave us be.
You must live.
Hold on until the
Heart-Piercing Curse is broken
or your two brothers find you.
You really think I can't
kill the Demon Orb?
It's just a matter of time.
Once you're dead,
I have a hundred
ways to destroy him.
I just want to have
a meaningful death.
Why won't you let me die?
Why won't you?
If your trade your
life for ours,
do you think we
could live in peace?
Nezha.
No, mom.
It'll hurt you.
It's okay.
This is the end.
Just want to hug
you one last time.
Mom.
I guess I won't get
to see you grow up.
From now on,
you'll have to
walk your own path.
I... I'm useless.
So useless.
I was born a demon,
and have always caused you pain.
I wanted so badly,
to make you proud.
This is all my fault.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
Every day I spent with you,
I was so happy.
I never cared
whether you were an immortal
or a demon.
All I know is
you are my son.
Mommy
will always
love...
Nezha, stay calm!
Stop!
Your body will be torn apart!
The True Fire of Samadhi
has compensated for
the fire needed for
the body restoration.
Nezha's physical form
is complete now!
Dad,
take care of Mom.
Help me break the cauldron!
Oh no!
They are absorbing the energy
of the Tianyuan Cauldron!
Roota Maxima!
Demon Hunters, by my command,
march!
Father,
you need to save your
energy for self-protection.
We've been backing down
for far too long.
We thought if we
gave everything,
then Wuliang would let us live.
But in the end, they
still want us dead.
If that's what they want,
then we'll fight them to death!
Yes, let's fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
We can't let them out!
Do not give up!
Hang in there!
Make it...
break!
The cauldron!
My cauldron!
There goes the
foundation of Chan Sect!
Kill all these bastards!
Attack!
You ungrateful traitors.
Can't tell right from wrong!
Roaring Dragon Waves!
So those two minions of
his are monsters too.
Demons, immortals,
it's all part of your trickery!
You despicable lowlife.
How dare you oppose me!
Witness my true powers!
I'll give you two
one last chance because
I value talents.
Surrender now
and I'll grant you immortality.
Hell with immortality!
I'm all demon.
So what?
You claim to be a guiding light,
but all you do is
bully the weak,
and bring chaos to the world.
You are the real evil!
Ignorant fools,
the immortals rule the world.
Siding with the powerful
is the only way out.
Either accept that or
you'll have no place to run to.
If there is no way ahead,
then I will carve out a path!
If the world won't
accommodate me,
I will turn the
world upside down!
Master!
My face...
You...
You fools broke
my Ageless Spell!
Old fart.
Ba... back to the palace.
Wait for me!
My father plans to
lead the dragons
deep into the
ocean to hide away.
Now that your
identity is exposed,
why don't you come with us?
No.
I used to keep hiding
and running away,
until there was
nowhere to left to go.
Now I finally know how
to face this world.
Wuliang is one of the
most powerful immortals
and is trusted by
the Supreme Lord.
He may not fall so easily.
Plus, immortals and demons
walk different paths,
like water and fire.
Immortals, demons...
Those are just excuses for
controlling those who are different.
So what?
You think you can change that?
I want to try.
Perhaps I'm too old
to fight against the world.
Ao Bing.
I know that
once you've made up your mind,
you'll always follow through.
My son,
in the past,
I put too much burden on you.
I never even
listened to you carefully.
I apologize.
I only wanted to use my experience
to give you a good life.
But now I see,
the experience of
the older generation
is but the past,
and may not be right for you.
You must walk your own path.
From now on,
follow your heart.
Knew you'd come back.
Why?
Because we are both too young.
Too naive to know the
limits of the world.
Master.
Your face...
Don't worry.
Crana has helped
apply some medicine.
With Tianyuan
Cauldron destroyed,
Chan Sect no longer has
a guaranteed victory.
We've committed a grave sin.
We must act before the Supreme
Lord returns from seclusion.
Come,
let's go see him.
Is the holding cell
concealed well?
Nobody else can come in here.
The cell inside is
shielded with a spell.
The door can only be opened
by you and one other guard only.
Mmm.
Slacking off.
Snoozing on the job.
What is going on?
This door
uses facial recognition.
Your appearance has changed,
and will need to be re-entered.
Redo it.
You dare to laugh at me?
Curse you to sleep
for ten years.
Are you suffering,
Brother?
Brother is the one
who has suffered.
Who has... has beat
you up like this?
Hmph.
Do you know why I
recruited you in the past?
I wanted your demon identity
so that in the Deification War,
I could entrust you
with important tasks.
You're delusional!
Father [Shen Zhengdao]
Don't worry.
He's still breathing.
If you will let me
place a curse on you,
then your father can enjoy
a peaceful life at Yu Xu Palace.
The two people you've
asked for are here.
Think carefully about it.
Hm?
The medicine from
earlier has taken effect.
Then what can we do?
Who else can open the door?
Ten years...
Jinzha of Five Dragon
Mountain, Yunxiao Cave.
[Jinzha] Jinzha of Five
Dragon Mountain, Yunxiao Cave.
Muzha of Jiugong Mountain,
White Egret Cave. [Jinzha]
[Muzha] Muzha of Jiugong Mountain,
Responding the summons
to return to palace.
Master.
Bear with it.
That should be enough.
I think
the left eye isn't
swollen enough.
The right cheek
needs adjustment.
Wait!
Were you two laughing just now?
I dare not.
Master is suffering
and my heart hurts a
hundred times more.
Really?
Absolutely true.
Heaven and earth bears witness.
Okay, that's enough.
I think
we overdid it.
What?
It's alright.
Apply some medicine
and we'll try again.
Master, you are one who
accomplishes great things.
This is for the fate
of the Chan Sect.
Let's try a few more times.
We will get it right eventually.
Catch him!
Don't let him run!
Hurry,
put on the medicine quickly!
Medicine!
Let me go!